leaf4 = [
    {"question":"礦工","Answer":"kuànggōng"},
{"question":"姿態","Answer":"zītài"},
{"question":"專注","Answer":"zhuānzhù"},
{"question":"毫無生氣","Answer":"háowúshēngqì"},
{"question":"窗簾","Answer":"chuānglián"},
{"question":"猶豫","Answer":"yóuyù"},
{"question":"無奈","Answer":"wúnài"},
{"question":"竟然","Answer":"jìngrán"},
{"question":"緩慢","Answer":"huǎnmàn"},
{"question":"依舊","Answer":"yījiù"},
{"question":"攀附","Answer":"pānfù"},
{"question":"破舊","Answer":"pòjiù"},
{"question":"磚牆","Answer":"zhuānqiáng"},
{"question":"漫長","Answer":"màncháng"},
{"question":"爬山虎","Answer":"páshānhǔ"},
{"question":"葉柄","Answer":"yèbǐng"},
{"question":"呈現","Answer":"chéngxiàn"},
{"question":"鮮","Answer":"xiān"},
{"question":"枯黃","Answer":"kūhuáng"},
{"question":"瓊絲","Answer":"qióngsī"},
{"question":"颳風","Answer":"guā fēng"},
{"question":"遲早","Answer":"chízǎo"},
{"question":"默不作聲","Answer":"mòbùzuòshēng"},
{"question":"依然","Answer":"yīrán"},
{"question":"凝視","Answer":"níngshì"},
{"question":"喚蘇","Answer":"huànsū"},
{"question":"煮食爐","Answer":"zhǔshí lú"},
{"question":"雞湯","Answer":"jītāng"},
{"question":"堅持","Answer":"jiānchí"},
{"question":"拿波里","Answer":"ná bōlǐ"},
{"question":"檢查","Answer":"jiǎnchá"},
{"question":"臨走","Answer":"línzǒu"},
{"question":"欣慰","Answer":"xīnwèi"},
{"question":"痊愈","Answer":"quányù"},
{"question":"貝阿蒙","Answer":"bèi āméng"},
{"question":"患","Answer":"huàn"},
{"question":"肺炎","Answer":"fèiyán"},
{"question":"面臨","Answer":"miànlín"},
{"question":"微笑","Answer":"wēixiào"},
{"question":"度過","Answer":"dùguò"},
{"question":"關","Answer":"guān"},
{"question":"毛線","Answer":"máoxiàn"},
{"question":"織","Answer":"zhī"},
{"question":"圍巾","Answer":"wéijīn"},
{"question":"孤零零","Answer":"gūlínglíng"},
{"question":"獨自 ","Answer":"dúzì  "},
{"question":"呻吟","Answer":"shēnyín"},
{"question":"濕透","Answer":"shītòu"},
{"question":"寒顫","Answer":"hánchàn"},
{"question":"烈 ","Answer":"liè  "}
]